{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"10.0.1","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":1590,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":12,"width":640,"height":480,"responsive":false,"scalable":false,"launchFile":"index.html"},"contentStructure":[{"id":"si25468","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_331","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_331","title":"Information Security Awareness Quiz --Working Remotely-- ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_574","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_574","title":"Take our Security Quiz   to test your knowledge.    Click on Begin to start. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_575","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_575","title":"Brought to you by the Information Security Branch  Office of the Chief Information Officer ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_9","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si21887","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si21901","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide21706","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si25468","Text_Caption_331","Text_Caption_574","Text_Caption_575","Button_9","si21887","si21901"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide21706"}}},{"id":"Image_189","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_189","roles":{}},{"id":"si12441","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_338","roles":{}},{"id":"si12349","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_327","title":"Threat actors are taking advantage of the Covid-19. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12360","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_328","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12364","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_329","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12360_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si12382","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_332","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12386","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_333","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12382_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12435","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_337","roles":{}},{"id":"si12459","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_42","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12473","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_43","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19347","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19361","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19593","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19606","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19621","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19634","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19649","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19662","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19677","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19690","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25507","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Question Title ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12405","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_334","title":"Correct - Answer: A  Corporations, governments and individuals have noticed attackers are using the global pandemic as an opportunity to spread malware via Covid19-themed emails, apps, websites and social media. Please be aware of this risk and do your best to fact check any Covid-19 related content you receive.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12417","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_335","title":"Incorrect  - Answer: A  Corporations, governments and individuals have noticed attackers are using the global pandemic as an opportunity to spread malware via Covid19-themed emails, apps, websites and social media. Please be aware of this risk and do your best to fact check any Covid-19 related content you receive.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12429","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_336","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12483","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_189","si12349","si12364","si12386","si12459","si12473","si19347","si19361","si19593","si19606","si19621","si19634","si19649","si19662","si19677","si19690","si25507","si12429"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12483"},"question":{"interactionId":"12329","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Threat actors are taking advantage of the Covid-19.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_190","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_190","roles":{}},{"id":"si22070","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_714","roles":{}},{"id":"si21978","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_698","title":"2.  All Wi-Fi networks with passwords are reliable. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21989","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_704","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21993","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_705","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21989_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_394","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22000","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_706","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22004","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_707","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22000_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_395","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si22064","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_713","roles":{}},{"id":"si22092","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_103","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22110","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_104","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22132","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_105","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22150","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_106","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22162","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22174","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22186","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22198","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22210","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22222","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22234","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22246","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22058","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_712","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22046","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_711","title":"Incorrect - Answer: Answer: B  Wi-Fi networks with passwords are not fully reliable as criminals can discover the password. if someone else has the password for the Wi-Fi network you’re using, then with a little effort, they can snoop on your traffic as if it were an open network. Ensure that you are choosing complicated passwords for your network and sharing it only with trusted parties. If you are using a password protected network that you don’t fully trust it, then remember to avoid doing any confidential work.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22034","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_710","title":"Correct - Answer: B  Wi-Fi networks with passwords are not fully reliable as criminals can discover the password. if someone else has the password for the Wi-Fi network you’re using, then with a little effort, they can snoop on your traffic as if it were an open network. Ensure that you are choosing complicated passwords for your network and sharing it only with trusted parties. If you are using a password protected network that you don’t fully trust it, then remember to avoid doing any confidential work.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide22259","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_190","si21978","si21993","si22004","si22092","si22110","si22132","si22150","si22162","si22174","si22186","si22198","si22210","si22222","si22234","si22246","si22058"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide22259"},"question":{"interactionId":"21958","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"2.  All Wi-Fi networks with passwords are reliable.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_191","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_191","roles":{}},{"id":"si22393","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_725","roles":{}},{"id":"si22301","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_699","title":"3. What is the best Wi-Fi router security? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22312","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_715","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22316","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_716","title":"Wi-Fi Protected Access (WPA)  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22312_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_397","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Wi-Fi Protected Access (WPA) \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22323","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_717","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22327","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_718","title":"Wi-Fi Protected Access II (WPA2) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22323_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_398","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Wi-Fi Protected Access II (WPA2)\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si24957","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24961","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Wired Equivalent Privacy (WEP) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24957_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Wired Equivalent Privacy (WEP)\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22387","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_724","roles":{}},{"id":"si22415","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_107","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22433","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_108","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22455","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_109","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22473","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_110","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22485","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22497","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22509","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22521","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22533","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22545","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22557","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22569","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22357","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_721","title":"Correct - Answer: B  Wired Equivalent Privacy (WEP) is the oldest and increasingly vulnerable form of Wi-Fi encryption and should not be used.  Wi-Fi Protected Access (WPA) is improved but has been identified as being vulnerable to intrusion.  While no Wi-Fi is 100% secure (unless we refrain from using it), the next generation Wi-Fi Protected Access, WPA2, is currently the most secure choice.  Check the ‘wireless security’ or ‘wireless network’ settings page in your router’s administration console for your encryption type.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22369","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_722","title":"Incorrect  - Answer: B  Wired Equivalent Privacy (WEP) is the oldest and increasingly vulnerable form of Wi-Fi encryption and should not be used.  Wi-Fi Protected Access (WPA) is improved but has been identified as being vulnerable to intrusion.  While no Wi-Fi is 100% secure (unless we refrain from using it), the next generation Wi-Fi Protected Access, WPA2, is currently the most secure choice.  Check the ‘wireless security’ or ‘wireless network’ settings page in your router’s administration console for your encryption type.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22381","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_723","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide22582","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_191","si22301","si22316","si22327","si24961","si22415","si22433","si22455","si22473","si22485","si22497","si22509","si22521","si22533","si22545","si22557","si22569","si22381"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide22582"},"question":{"interactionId":"22281","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"3. What is the best Wi-Fi router security?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_192","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_192","roles":{}},{"id":"si22716","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_736","roles":{}},{"id":"si22624","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_700","title":"4. What do you call a rogue device connected to your wireless network? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22635","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_726","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22639","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_727","title":"Wireless Intruder ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22635_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Wireless Intruder\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si22646","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_728","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22650","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_729","title":"Rogue Ransomer ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22646_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Rogue Ransomer\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si22657","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_730","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22661","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_731","title":"Cyber Surfer ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22657_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Cyber Surfer\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22928","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22932","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Beacon Hacker  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22928_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Beacon Hacker\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22710","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_735","roles":{}},{"id":"si22738","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_111","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22756","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_112","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22778","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_113","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22796","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_114","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22808","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22820","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22832","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22844","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22856","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22868","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22880","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22892","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22680","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_732","title":"Correct -  Answer: A  A rouge device on our network is a Wireless Intruder. Wireless Intruders can range from an accidental ‘bandwidth borrowing’ neighbour to a hacker.  Ensure you have a WPA2 encrypted router with a strong password and consider engaging further wireless network protection (see next question).  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22692","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_733","title":"Incorrect  -  Answer: A  A rouge device on our network is a Wireless Intruder. Wireless Intruders can range from an accidental ‘bandwidth borrowing’ neighbour to a hacker.  Ensure you have a WPA2 encrypted router with a strong password and consider engaging further wireless network protection (see next question).  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22704","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_734","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide22905","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_192","si22624","si22639","si22650","si22661","si22932","si22738","si22756","si22778","si22796","si22808","si22820","si22832","si22844","si22856","si22868","si22880","si22892","si22704"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide22905"},"question":{"interactionId":"22604","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"4. What do you call a rogue device connected to your wireless network?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_193","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_193","roles":{}},{"id":"si23144","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_749","roles":{}},{"id":"si23041","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_701","title":"5.  How can you prevent a ‘Wireless Intruder’? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23052","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_737","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23056","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_738","title":"Ensure you have encryption and a strong password protecting your router ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23052_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Ensure you have encryption and a strong password protecting your router\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23063","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_739","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23067","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_740","title":"Monitor connected devices to your Wi-Fi ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23063_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Monitor connected devices to your Wi-Fi\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23074","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_741","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23078","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_742","title":"Get an IP scanner tool to detect a network intrusion ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23074_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Get an IP scanner tool to detect a network intrusion\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23085","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_743","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23089","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_744","title":"All of the above  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23085_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"All of the above\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si23138","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_748","roles":{}},{"id":"si23166","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_115","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23184","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_116","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23206","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_117","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23224","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_118","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23236","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23248","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23260","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23272","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23284","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23296","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23308","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23320","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23108","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_745","title":"Correct - Answer: D  Even with a strong password and encryption, you may have one (or many) intruders on your wireless network.  The easiest way to prevent this is to frequently change your router password. There are also many wireless watcher or IP scanning tools that can be downloaded (some for free) to warn you when a rogue device has or is connected.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23120","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_746","title":"Incorrect  - Answer: D  Even with a strong password and encryption, you may have one (or many) intruders on your wireless network.  The easiest way to prevent this is to frequently change your router password. There are also many wireless watcher or IP scanning tools that can be downloaded (some for free) to warn you when a rogue device has or is connected.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23132","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_747","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide23333","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_193","si23041","si23056","si23067","si23078","si23089","si23166","si23184","si23206","si23224","si23236","si23248","si23260","si23272","si23284","si23296","si23308","si23320","si23132"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide23333"},"question":{"interactionId":"23021","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"5.  How can you prevent a ‘Wireless Intruder’?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_194","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_194","roles":{}},{"id":"si23482","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_763","roles":{}},{"id":"si23379","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_750","title":"6.  You can feel reasonably secure when using VPN at a Wi-Fi hotspot. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23390","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_751","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23394","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_752","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23390_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_407","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si23401","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_753","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23405","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_754","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23401_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_408","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23476","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_762","roles":{}},{"id":"si23504","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_119","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23522","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_120","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23544","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_121","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23562","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_122","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23574","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23586","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23598","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23610","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23622","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23634","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23646","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23658","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23446","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_759","title":"Correct - Answer:  A  Even though a hacker can intercept your signal and attempt to gain access to your information, the information will be encrypted and therefore unusable.  This should be the only instance that you would consider using a password-protected site as these sites store your credentials and allow access to sensitive information.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23458","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_760","title":"Incorrect  - Answer:  A  Even though a hacker can intercept your signal and attempt to gain access to your information, the information will be encrypted and therefore unusable.  This should be the only instance that you would consider using a password-protected site as these sites store your credentials and allow access to sensitive information.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23470","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_761","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide23671","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_194","si23379","si23394","si23405","si23504","si23522","si23544","si23562","si23574","si23586","si23598","si23610","si23622","si23634","si23646","si23658","si23470"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide23671"},"question":{"interactionId":"23359","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"6.  You can feel reasonably secure when using VPN at a Wi-Fi hotspot.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_195","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_195","roles":{}},{"id":"si23820","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_777","roles":{}},{"id":"si23717","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_764","title":"7.  Apps from a reputable ‘app store’ are always safe to use on Wi-Fi. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23728","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_765","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23732","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_766","title":"True\t ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23728_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_411","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True\t\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23739","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_767","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23743","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_768","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23739_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_412","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si23814","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_776","roles":{}},{"id":"si23842","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_123","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23860","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_124","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23882","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_125","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23900","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_126","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23912","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23924","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23936","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23948","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23960","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23972","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23984","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23996","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23784","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_773","title":"Correct - Answer:  B  Many third party apps are designed with the express purpose to collect user data and/or install malware unbeknownst to the owner of the device; that is why it is recommended to always procure your apps from a reputable ‘app store’ such as Google Play and Play Store. Please remember that there are still documented scams occurring within the best app stores and no app is safe to use if it is not kept up-to-date with patches to mitigate vulnerabilities.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23796","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_774","title":"Incorrect  -  Answer:  B  Many third party apps are designed with the express purpose to collect user data and/or install malware unbeknownst to the owner of the device; that is why it is recommended to always procure your apps from a reputable ‘app store’ such as Google Play and Play Store. Please remember that there are still documented scams occurring within the best app stores and no app is safe to use if it is not kept up-to-date with patches to mitigate vulnerabilities.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23808","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_775","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide24009","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_195","si23717","si23732","si23743","si23842","si23860","si23882","si23900","si23912","si23924","si23936","si23948","si23960","si23972","si23984","si23996","si23808"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide24009"},"question":{"interactionId":"23697","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"7.  Apps from a reputable ‘app store’ are always safe to use on Wi-Fi.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_199","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_199","roles":{}},{"id":"si25203","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_815","roles":{}},{"id":"si25089","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_793","title":"8.  If you receive an email related to Covid-19, what are some ways to recognize and avoid coronavirus-themed phishing emails? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25100","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_801","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25104","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_802","title":"Beware of online requests for personal information ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25100_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_423","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Beware of online requests for personal information\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si25111","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_803","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25115","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_804","title":"Check the email address or link ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25111_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_424","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Check the email address or link\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si25559","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25563","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Watch for spelling and grammatical mistakes ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25559_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Watch for spelling and grammatical mistakes\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si25574","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25578","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Look for generic greetings ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25574_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Look for generic greetings\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si25589","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25593","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"All of the above  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25589_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"All of the above\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si25197","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_814","roles":{}},{"id":"si25225","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_132","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide25392q7","for":"Slide25392q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25243","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_133","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide25392q7","for":"Slide25392q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25265","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_134","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide25392q7","for":"Slide25392q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25283","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_135","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide25392q7","for":"Slide25392q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25295","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide25392q7","for":"Slide25392q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25307","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide25392q7","for":"Slide25392q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25319","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide25392q7","for":"Slide25392q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25331","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide25392q7","for":"Slide25392q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25343","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide25392q7","for":"Slide25392q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25355","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide25392q7","for":"Slide25392q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25367","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide25392q7","for":"Slide25392q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25379","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide25392q7","for":"Slide25392q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25167","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_811","title":"Correct - Answer:  E  The correct answer is all of the above. Like other types of phishing emails, the email messages usually try to lure you into clicking on a link or providing personal information that can be used to commit fraud or identity theft. For more information you can check out Cyber Hygiene for COVID-19 released by the Canadian Centre for Cyber Security. https://cyber.gc.ca/en/guidance/cyber-hygiene-covid-19  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25179","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_812","title":"Incorrect  -  Answer:  E  The correct answer is all of the above. Like other types of phishing emails, the email messages usually try to lure you into clicking on a link or providing personal information that can be used to commit fraud or identity theft. For more information you can check out Cyber Hygiene for COVID-19 released by the Canadian Centre for Cyber Security. https://cyber.gc.ca/en/guidance/cyber-hygiene-covid-19  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25191","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_813","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide25392","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_199","si25089","si25104","si25115","si25563","si25578","si25593","si25225","si25243","si25265","si25283","si25295","si25307","si25319","si25331","si25343","si25355","si25367","si25379","si25191"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide25392"},"question":{"interactionId":"25069","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"8.  If you receive an email related to Covid-19, what are some ways to recognize and avoid coronavirus-themed phishing emails?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["E"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_202","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_202","roles":{}},{"id":"si25802","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_830","roles":{}},{"id":"si25688","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_794","title":"9.   Due to Covid-19 many companies are now turning to Virtual Private Networks (VPN’s) to provide secure connectivity for remote workers. Which of the below answers will insure VPN security? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25699","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_816","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25703","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_817","title":"Keeping VPNs up to date by applying the latest patches ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25699_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_429","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Keeping VPNs up to date by applying the latest patches\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si25710","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_818","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25714","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_819","title":"Notifying employees of an expected increase in phishing attempts ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25710_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_430","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Notifying employees of an expected increase in phishing attempts\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si25721","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_820","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25725","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_821","title":"Requiring employees to use strong passwords to defend against attacks ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25721_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"431","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Requiring employees to use strong passwords to defend against attacks\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si25732","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_822","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25736","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_823","title":"Testing VPN infrastructure limitations in preparation for mass usage ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25732_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"433","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Testing VPN infrastructure limitations in preparation for mass usage\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si25743","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_824","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25747","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_825","title":"Insuring employees use VPN only when necessary as to not overload it ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25743_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"435","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Insuring employees use VPN only when necessary as to not overload it\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si25999","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"F) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26003","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"All of the above  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25999_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"All of the above\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si25796","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_829","roles":{}},{"id":"si25824","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_136","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide25991q8","for":"Slide25991q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25842","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_137","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide25991q8","for":"Slide25991q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25864","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_138","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide25991q8","for":"Slide25991q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25882","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_139","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide25991q8","for":"Slide25991q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25894","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide25991q8","for":"Slide25991q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25906","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide25991q8","for":"Slide25991q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25918","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide25991q8","for":"Slide25991q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25930","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide25991q8","for":"Slide25991q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25942","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide25991q8","for":"Slide25991q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25954","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide25991q8","for":"Slide25991q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25966","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide25991q8","for":"Slide25991q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25978","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide25991q8","for":"Slide25991q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25766","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_826","title":"Correct - Answer:  F  Organizations should ensure that they are keeping up their VPN security in the event of staff being unable to work locally. This means keeping VPNs up to date (apply the latest patches), ensuring employees only use VPN when necessary and that infostructure can handle mass logins and preparing employees for an increase in phishing attempts. To learn more check out https://www.cyber.gc.ca/en/guidance/telework-security-issues-itsap10016  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25778","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_827","title":"Incorrect  -  Answer:  F  Organizations should ensure that they are keeping up their VPN security in the event of staff being unable to work locally. This means keeping VPNs up to date (apply the latest patches), ensuring employees only use VPN when necessary and that infostructure can handle mass logins and preparing employees for an increase in phishing attempts. To learn more check out https://www.cyber.gc.ca/en/guidance/telework-security-issues-itsap10016  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25790","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_828","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide25991","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_202","si25688","si25703","si25714","si25725","si25736","si25747","si26003","si25824","si25842","si25864","si25882","si25894","si25906","si25918","si25930","si25942","si25954","si25966","si25978","si25790"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide25991"},"question":{"interactionId":"25668","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"9.   Due to Covid-19 many companies are now turning to Virtual Private Networks (VPN’s) to provide secure connectivity for remote workers. Which of the below answers will insure VPN security?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["F"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_185","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_185","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_107","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_107","title":"Quiz Results ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6059","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6083","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6091","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6055","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You Scored: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6079","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Total Questions: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6087","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Accuracy: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6103","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6107","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6121","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20489","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20502","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20517","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20530","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6038","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6038"}}},{"id":"si6231","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_186","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_186","roles":{}},{"id":"Button_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_4","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19054","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19068","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_9","title":" Stay Current With Information Security By Subscribing to the:   Weekly Security News Digest ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_298","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_298","title":"Thank you for taking the quiz.  To exit the quiz, close the browser window. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_198","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_198","roles":{}},{"id":"Slide6219","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si6231","Image_186","Button_4","si19054","si19068","SmartShape_9","Text_Caption_298","Image_198"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":600},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6219"}}},{"id":"Pool502","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":502,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"April2020Quiz","class":"project","title":"April2020Quiz","children":["Slide21706","Slide12483","Slide22259","Slide22582","Slide22905","Slide23333","Slide23671","Slide24009","Slide25392","Slide25991","Slide6038","Slide6219"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":458,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide12483q0","Slide22259q1","Slide22582q2","Slide22905q3","Slide23333q4","Slide23671q5","Slide24009q6","Slide25392q7","Slide25991q8"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":90,"passScore":72}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"quiz","CCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"SCCriteria":"quiz","SCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide21706","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide12483","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide22259","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide22582","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide22905","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide23333","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide23671","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide24009","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide25392","title":"Slide 9"},{"id":"Slide25991","title":"Slide 10"},{"id":"Slide6038","title":"Slide 11"},{"id":"Slide6219","title":"Slide 12"}]}